<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Horosc</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="exit">EXIT</string>
    <string name="birthdayHorscope">Birthday Horscope</string>
    <string name="zodiacsigns">Zodiac Signs</string>
    <string name="todaysHoroscope">Todays Horoscope</string>



    <string name="a">-----------------------------aries---------------------------------</string>


    <string name="ariesDescription">The symbol for this sign is that of a ram for good reason. Aries is full of life and possesses
    high energy, which makes this sign always looking for a challenge. The typical Aries person
    is full of vitality, curiosity, and has a heightened sense of justice. They often excel at anything where a bit of competition is involved, whether this is of a cognitive nature or
    physical. The challenge is the thing. If there is a chance to win, to best someone, to show
    off abilities, Aries is in it to win it. The Aries person feels most alive when they are in control
    and leading others. They are often impatient and abrupt with those whom they feel are not
    their equals and are in a leadership position. Most Aries do not like being told what to do if
    the person in charge is less talented than they


    \n\n


    Aries is a fire sign which means that they tend to have the characteristics of fire: warm,
    vital, and bright. They can sometimes be impulsive and have hot tempters. However, they
    have a deep desire to protect and when they have harmed someone in error they will be
    the first to make amends. They are optimistic and are not given to depressive interludes
    (which makes them also intolerant of those that do)</string>

    <string name="ariesUpside">Highly energetic, and has no problem working long hours on a single project. Often
    take the initiative experiencing new breakthroughs and discoveries. Aries are thorough,
    painstaking, and have a knack for precise records and clarity. They live hard, love hard, and
    play hard</string>

    <string name="ariesDownside"> Aries have tunnel vision when working on a project which can make them seem
    selfish. They can become impatient with those who are not similar to themselves
    temperamentally and intellectually. The dedication to a project can become stubbornness,
    possessiveness, and can lead to a withdrawn and sullen attitude. Many Aries who do not
    feel acknowledged for their accomplishments become sarcastic and rude</string>

    <string name="ariesHiddenSide">Talking very loud</string>
    <string name="ariesHabit">talking very loud</string>
    <string name="ariesFear">losing</string>



    <string name="b">-----------------------------virgo---------------------------------</string>

    <string name="virgoDescription">The cool, calm, clarity that this sign exudes is why the symbol of the Maiden was chosen.
    Virgo people are mild mannered on the surface, but underneath there is a flurry of activity.
    Their minds are never quiet; always thinking, calculating, assessing. They loves making
    something out of nothing, nurturing and growing small things. They tend to be extremely
    detail oriented and particularly like producing something that is not only useful, but beautiful
    and skillful



    \n\n


    Virgo don’t mind being alone as long as they know that they are appreciated and needed.
    They are sympathetic listeners, and are ready to help out those in need. Their good nature
    often makes them easy to take advantage of, and often they end up taking on more jobs
    and tasks than they should. This sign would do well to carefully consider the situation and
    the task before agreeing to take it on



    \n\n


    Virgo is an Earth sign which means that they love making something from the land with
    their own hands. They do not tend to be loud or bossy, but are brilliant strategists and an
    asset to any team. Very often they will overburden themselves and take on more than they should,
        which makes their work suffer

  </string>


    <string name="virgoUpside"> Virgo have a heart for their fellow man. They are kind, patient and love to laugh.
    They are not loud ‘look at me’ signs, but rather prefer to be the strong, silent type. They are
    creative thinkers and true family oriented people. Male Virgo, once they are committed to
    relationship never walk away (unless there is a betrayal, and even then it isn’t written in
    stone). Female Virgo are dedicated parents, often parenting other children in the
    neighborhood </string>


    <string name="virgoDownside"> Virgo are particularly attentive to health; theirs, yours, everyone’s, which can
    often lead to obsessive behaviors toward health (hypochondria). They can also be
    judgmental and critical of those that they feel are not living up to their potential, or are going
    about a project in an inefficient way. Virgo are opinionated and have no problem sharing
    their opinions, even when they should not </string>


    <string name="virgoHiddenSide">very selfless</string>

    <string name="virgoHabit">over-analyzing everything</string>

    <string name="virgoFear">losing people they love</string>


    <string name="c">-----------------------------taurus---------------------------------</string>

    <string name="taurusDescription"> Tarus’s symbol is the bull because this sign’s characteristic is to be peaceful and
    methodical. This sign is often very deliberate in their actions, relaxed, and enjoys all of the
    sensual pleasures that abound in this dimension. Food, drink, sex, luxury, are all sought
    after by the typical taruean. Because this sign loves luxury they are willing to work hard to
    obtain it. They are slow to anger, but once disturbed it can be volatile. Taurus signs look for
    stability in their lives and in their partners and co-workers. Taurus people are not in a hurry,
    typically, and it can take them many years to decide what it is that they would like to do for
    a living, or where they’d like to go on vacation. Many of this sign prefer to live in the country
    as they are drawn to the earth and the natural world. Earth signs tend to have solid,
    reputable natures, which coincides with the Earth



    \n\n

    Additionally, this sign takes a long time to fully commit to a relationship, but once they do
    they are in it for the long haul. Most Taurus males marry for life and are dedicated
    companions, parents, and lovers. Female Taurus are like male Taurus in that once they
    commit themselves to a relationship they are stubborn and slow to leave it. However, if
    Taurus women feel put upon, taken for granted, or unappreciated for long enough, they will
    leave
    </string>


    <string name="taurusUpside"> Taurus people almost always finish what they start. They are deliberate thinkers
    and when making decisions usually make the right one. Taurus are generally adaptable,
    adjusting easily to new circumstances especially if there is the reward of luxury, comfort, or
    sensual reward. This sign loves to laugh and spend time with family </string>


    <string name="taurusDownside"> Taurus can be stubborn and ‘bullish’ about ideas that they’ve adopted, which
    can also make them difficult to get along with when attempting to cooperate on a shared
    project. Taurus needs to be the leader and to be held in high esteem. If they are not, they
    refuse to work, often finding small ways to sabotage projects, relationships, or undermine
    authority that they deem unworthy of leadership </string>


    <string name="taurusHiddenSide">very caring</string>

    <string name="taurusHabit">not listening to anyone elese if they think they are right</string>

    <string name="taurusFear">getting publicly embarassed</string>


    <string name="d">-----------------------------scorpio---------------------------------</string>

    <string name="scorpioDescription"> The symbol for Scorpio is the scorpion. This creature was chosen because it typifies many
    of the characteristics of this sign. The scorpio person is not necessarily aggressive on its
    own, unless provoked and in general would rather be contemplative. They crave alone time
    and often become extremely annoyed when they don’t get it. Scorpio people are great secret keepers and feel each emotion more intensely than other signs. Perhaps because of
    this they are able to be quite discerning when assisting people with their problems. They
    are able to cut to the bottom line and show others the best and the worst in their lives




    \n\n

    Scorpio signs are not fearful individuals, often trying things that others would not attempt.
    This is because they most often become self-aware at an earlier age than most other signs.
    This also gives them a custodial feel toward other signs and they have an inflamed sense of
    justice when it comes to standing up for those who lack that ability. Scorpio signs are very
    interested in what makes people tick on the inside and are often in fields that allow them to
    discover things about the internal workings of others

    </string>


    <string name="scorpioUpside"> Scorpio exhibit extreme self-control in many areas, and as a result expect that of
    those around them. They are disciplined, protective and are very interested in others. They
    give of themselves but do expect the same in return. Scorpio males and females both need
    to be the leaders, and excel at problem solving and troubleshooting projects and situations </string>


    <string name="scorpioDownside"> Scorpio invented the term ‘vendetta’. Once a Scorpio is crossed, they don’t
    forget it. Female Scorpio are worse about this than they others, often going decades
    without making amends with friends and family. Scorpio also tend to be pessimistic, often
    seeing threats where there aren’t any, which can make them suspicious, stubborn and
    paranoid without cause </string>


    <string name="scorpioHiddenSide">very good</string>

    <string name="scorpioHabit">not trusting someone until they\'ve proven their worth</string>

    <string name="scorpioFear">death</string>



    <string name="f">-----------------------------sagitarius---------------------------------</string>

    <string name="sagitariusDescription"> The centaur is the symbol for this sign. In mythology, the centaur was half man and half
    horse, given to pursing pleasure. The centaur is shown with a bow, which he shoots.
    Wherever the arrow lands, the centaur follows, retrieves the arrow and shoots again. Those
    born under this sign will love travelling, discovering new things, meeting new people, and
    learning new things



    \n\n

    Sagittarians crave the freedom of the open road, both metaphorically and physically. They
    are most unhappy when they are tied to a normal routine and can become restless in
    situations where there is not enough variety involved. Because they travel so much and are
    eager to experience new things, those of this sign are fun to be around and often have
    large numbers of friends. They question everything and think that everyone should do the
    same
    </string>


    <string name="sagitariusUpside">Sagittarians are highly intelligent and love to be around intelligent people. They
    enjoy learning new things, traveling to new places, and experiencing unique adventures.
    Creativity is at the core of who they are and Sagittarians are often creating and recreating their living situations, work situations, and human relationships. Sagittarians are spiritually
    inclined and are among the types that would travel to the Himalayas to commune with the
    monks, or take the book, Eat, Pray, Love and go to each spot mentioned in its pages to
    seek their own enlightenment</string>


    <string name="sagitariusDownside"> Confining a Sagittarian and not allowing for ample space to roam will make this
    sign rude, and uncooperative. Sagittarians often come up with unrealistic, big plans, but
    lack the ability to follow through with them. This isn’t because they aren’t capable, but
    rather they can become sidetracked chasing another avenue of adventure or thought.
    Sagittarians are about the bigger picture and details often bog them down and bore them </string>


    <string name="sagitariusHiddenSide">very hurt</string>

    <string name="sagitariusHabit">telling it as it is</string>

    <string name="sagitariusFear">no freedom</string>


    <string name="g">-----------------------------pisces---------------------------------</string>

    <string name="piscesDescription"> The fish is the symbol given to this sign, primarily because fish live in a secretive and
    mysterious place. Pisces tend to be daydreamers, often dreaming up brilliant ideas and
    plans which they are unable to facilitate themselves. They have a happy and vibrant inner ife that few get to share or see. They are deeply caring about others and don’t like to see
    people become unhappy




    \n\n

    They are tremendously dedicated individuals, staying with companies for decades where
    others move from one job to the next. So, too, with relationships. Others may find Pisces
    difficult to get to know because they don’t often readily share their underlying passion and
    compassion. Pisces signs tend to be highly and deeply religious, and sometimes will go
    overboard with their devotion to their particular faith. This can also lead to intolerance and
    bigotry

    </string>


    <string name="piscesUpside"> Pisces are empathetic people, often feeling badly for someone whose life is not
    going well. They feel the need to reach out to those who are less fortunate and will often
    find themselves involved in drama that they hadn’t intended. They are kind, caring
    individuals who feel everything deeply, even though you would not know it on the surface.
    They can be creative and imaginative when they believe that they have support to make
    those leaps </string>


    <string name="piscesDownside"> Because they feel everything so intensely, this sign can often become a clinical
    worrier. They will worry that they are not worrying. This tendency to worry also leads to
    indecision on their part, fearing that if they make a decision that others disagree with that
    they will have upset someone. Pisces don’t like to hurt people’s feelings and as such
    become conflicted when they have to make decisions. They do not do well as leaders, but
    are impressive support personnel. Sometimes the have a lack of follow through due to this
    indecisiveness and require a gentle nudge from other signs to complete tasks on time </string>


    <string name="piscesHiddenSide">very lazy</string>

    <string name="piscesHabit">falling asleep everywhere</string>

    <string name="piscesFear">rejection</string>


    <string name="h">-----------------------------leo---------------------------------</string>

    <string name="leoDescription"> The lion is the symbol for this sign because the lion embodies the best characteristics of
    the leo; proud, regal, relaxed, and in charge. Leo people know they are in charge, even
    when it may seem outwardly that they are not




    \n\n


        Leo signs tend to like relaxation, preferably someplace warm and comfortable. Leo likes
        the big picture, not the small details and fine print. Things that are too complicated,
        involved, or boring, they have no patience for. They are natural leaders and don’t often do
        well in situations where they have to take orders from others


        Love is king to a leo. To love and be loved is a driving motivation for this sign. Leos, not
        unlike the lion of a pride, need to be adored. If they are ignored or go unrecognized for
        some contribution they will feel hurt. All leos like to know that they have been seen and
        appreciated

        Fire signs, like Leo, are warm, bright individuals that use that energy and warmth to draw
        people to them. When the right balance is struck with a leo, those around this sign will feel
        as loved and appreciated as the leo in their midst


    \n\n



    </string>


    <string name="leoUpside"> Leo tend to be honest and decent people, opting to do the right thing regardless of
    the situation. They love organization so that they can find their ‘things’. Leos love material
    goods and luxury and want those that they love to experience this wealth as well. Leo are
    generally accepting of everyone initially and make decent, lasting relationships </string>


    <string name="leoDownside">  Leo have a great sense of self-worth which can cross the line into arrogance.
    Leo can tend toward extravagance if they are not satisfied with what they have. Because
    they like to be in charge, they can often become smothering to their mates and friends,
    which may leave them alone (which Leo hates). Divorce and loss are devastating to this
    sign as they are all about the community and family </string>


    <string name="leoHiddenSide">very confused</string>

    <string name="leoHabit">always wanting to win</string>

    <string name="leoFear">not being able to communicate</string>


    <string name="i">-----------------------------libra---------------------------------</string>

    <string name="libraDescription"> Libra people tend to need balance in their lives like no other sign of the zodiac, which
    makes the symbol of the scales particularly appropriate for this sign. Libra people need to
    keep a balance between work lives and recreational lives and an equal balance in their
    emotional and spiritual/physical lives. Because of this need Libra signs can sometimes seem wishy-washy when they are asked to make a decision. This is because they must
    ‘weigh’ all of their options. However, rest assured, that when a Libra makes up their mind
    the decision is likely to be the best win/win for all involved; benefiting the most people. This
    sign does not like to see people unhappy


    \n\n


        Harmony and peace are key to making this sign happy. When things are balanced, then
        there is harmony. This sign is often charming and people like to be around them and the
        only time that they will become unhappy is when they perceive that they have been treated
        unfairly. This sign does really well to embrace some form of meditation as it allows them to
        find that internal balance that will allow the outer balance to manifest itself. Most Libra enjoy
        physical exercise that involves some mental component, such as long distance running, or
        yoga. Many run marathons

    </string>


    <string name="libraUpside"> Libra all have a sense of fair play about them and become completely upset if they
    perceive that something is unfair or unjust. They are prone to talking for long periods of time
    about their favorite subjects. Generally the decisions that a Libra makes are the ones that
    will benefit the most people. Libra are often self-sacrificing for the good of the team or the
    family </string>


    <string name="libraDownside"> Because Libra take so long to make decisions it can be perceived as laziness,
    or absent- mindedness. Libra, because of their sense of justice and fair play, will often
    become argumentative to the exclusion of decorum or appropriateness. Libra don’t like to
    be in charge, but they like to have a say and to be heard </string>


    <string name="libraHiddenSide">very narcissistic</string>

    <string name="libraHabit">taking forever to make a decision</string>

    <string name="libraFear">being taken advantage of</string>


    <string name="j">-----------------------------gemni---------------------------------</string>

    <string name="gemniDescription"> The Gemini symbol is that of a pair of twins. This is because this sign rarely likes to do
    anything alone. Gemini are never happier than when they are sharing ideas and concepts
    with someone else. Communication is a key element for this sign, so many of this sign go
    into occupations that include some communication in some large capacity. Curiosity is a
    key characteristic of this sign, and they are people persons. Gemini are great at parties
    because they can find almost anything to talk about with anyone. Gemini are adventurous
    by nature and so engage in traveling as often as they can as it affords them the opportunity
    to meet new people, experience new ideas, and to learn new concepts


    \n\n

        Gemini are air signs, which means that they have light, airy personalities, with an
        effervescence that seems to draw people to them. This sign craves intellectual stimulation
        and often will push the envelope physically, mentally, and spiritually. If someone were to
        live out the book, Eat, Pray, Love it would be this sign as they are gluttons for new
        experiences, sometimes out of the box and out of the way experiences and people. This sign is also incredibly creative and are given to giant leaps of intuition, which makes them
        great entrepreneurs, designers, writers, speakers, and anything artistic. They love bright
        vibrant colors

        </string>


    <string name="gemniUpside"> Gemini are great conversationalists, and are charming people. Interesting to speak
    with, Gemini know a little bit about a lot of things. They have a great sense of humor and
    are generally optimistic people. Gemini often make their own fun, despising boredom </string>


    <string name="gemniDownside"> Gemini like to be the center of attention; always. When they perceive the
    situation to not be in their favor, they leave it. This can include relationships, careers, and
    friendships. Because of this need to be seen as important, Gemini will sometimes stretch
    the truth. When they are focused only on themselves they can be largely unsympathetic
    and rude. Male Gemini tend to change jobs often, and female Gemini change partners
    often due to boredom </string>


    <string name="gemniHiddenSide">very forgiving</string>

    <string name="gemniHabit">not giving the other person a chance to speak</string>

    <string name="gemniFear">getting too attached</string>


    <string name="k">-----------------------------aquarius---------------------------------</string>

    <string name="aquariusDescription"> The man who carries the pitcher of water is the symbol for this sign. This is because
    Aquarians are often generous with their time and resources. For this reason this sign often
    find themselves in occupations where they are helping on some humanitarian level. They are interested and have a deep concern for the welfare of others. They never know a
    stranger and are generally loved by all around them. Aquarians never meet a stranger and
    often will go out of their way to meet with people that they’ve not heard from for years.
    Connection is at the core of this sign



    \n\n



    Fascinated by all things gadget, many Aquarians enjoy tinkering with inventions and
    processes. On the surface, Aquarius people are often not very emotional, because they are
    more concerned with the exchanging of ideas and how they might better assist someone in
    their cause. Aquarians have a great deal of patience and tolerance for their fellow man.
    They make excellent teachers and relief aid workers, though do not become personally
    involved with them </string>


    <string name="aquariusUpside"> Aquarians are among the friendliest of the signs, making friends everywhere. They
    are often chosen among co-workers and family for special awards and honors because of
    their ability to network. Highly intelligent they are energetic and talented, often using their
    abilities to help others. Despite their extensive people skills, they often crave alone time to
    reflect and think about things. Meditation is recommended for this sign as it helps to
    maintain that sense of alone time, while at the same time a feeling of connectedness with
    something greater than themselves </string>


    <string name="aquariusDownside"> If this sign does not have alone time and time to do much desired reflection,
    they become dour, emotionless, and even are prone to depressive interludes. They can
    become highly resentful if they believe that their voice is not being truly heard or valued.
    Because they do self-reflect, this sign can become quite eccentric in some of the hobbies
    that they pursue, or activities they enjoy </string>


    <string name="aquariusHiddenSide">very emotional</string>

    <string name="aquariusHabit">zoning out in the middle of conversations</string>

    <string name="aquariusFear">falling in love</string>


    <string name="l">-----------------------------cancer---------------------------------</string>


    <string name="cancerDescription"> The crab symbolizes this sign for good reason. Just as the crab carries its own shell on its
    back, so too, does the typical cancerian…so to speak. The typical cancer person is all
    about home and family and is very dedicated and loyal to friends and family. Crabs often
    move sideways instead of moving in a straight line, and so will the person of this sign




    \n\n



    Often, if it will avoid a fight, or achieve the goal, then moving in alternative directions to
    arrive at the destination is typical. They tend to grasp and hold tightly those things that
    make them happy, and never let go. The key characteristic of this sign is that Cancer
    people need to be needed. They need to know that they matter to someone and that they
    are secure in that love. Brave, courageous, protective, all describe the best possible traits
    of this sign. Shy, reserved, brooding, and moody, do not serve the cancer person well, but
    may surface if their needs are not being met




    \n\n



    Cancer is a water sign which means that they have a deep, mysterious side to them that
    can also be gentle and nurturing

    </string>


    <string name="cancerUpside"> Cancer have an offbeat sense of humor, often finding something humorous that
    others don’t. They are extremely good listeners and have a heart for the problems of
    others. In fact, many gravitate toward this sign because they intuitively know that a Cancer
    will understand. When a Cancer becomes your friend you can be sure that they are truly
    your friend and will not consider using someone to their own benefit. Cancer tend to be
    dependable and reliable. They will tell you anything you want to know about them without
    blinking an eye as they are drawn to honesty in others as well as themselves </string>


    <string name="cancerDownside"> This sign can be moody, clingy, and often become incredibly insecure if they
    feel that they are about to lose the friendship or love of someone close to them. If the
    situation calls for it, they will lie, but often this dishonesty stems from a deep insecurity
    about being alone </string>


    <string name="cancerHiddenSide">very strong</string>

    <string name="cancerHabit">overreacting</string>

    <string name="cancerFear">being alone</string>


    <string name="m">-----------------------------capricorn---------------------------------</string>

    <string name="capricornDescription"> The mountain goat is the symbol for this sign because of the characteristic of the goat to
    climb higher and higher without losing his footing. Capricorn people are the type that are
    goal oriented and driven to succeed despite all odds. They will work long and hard hours toward a purposeful goal. Self-disciplined and successful, it is no wonder that some of the
    world’s greatest scientists, leaders, and teachers have been Capricorn




    \n\n



    Achievement is everything to a Capricorn. For this reason they tend to take life very
    seriously and are not tolerant of those who do not. They are also very good at state’s craft
    engaging in mental parrying at a high level. They are natural born leaders, politicians,
    mathematicians, and diplomats. Capricorn people tend to guard their hearts closely and
    well. To get close to a Capricorn may take some time, but once achieved, well worth it
    </string>


    <string name="capricornUpside"> Capricorns are the superheroes when It comes to making realistic, logical
    decisions. Their ability to cut through the red tape and see the bottom line is what makes
    them a real asset to any relationship or occupation where teamwork is valued. Capricorn
    are family oriented, but will keep their distance if the family is perceived to be violent,
    harmful, or unfulfilling. Capricorn have a dry sense of humor and their sarcastic wit is only
    appreciated by those who find humor everywhere. Highly intellectual, good with numbers
    and analysis, this sign is not often loud, but they are most definitely the muscle and the
    power behind the very successful machine </string>


    <string name="capricornDownside"> Because they are so dedicated to the big picture and the minute details, they
    can seem dull to others, who don’t understand the active internal nature of the Capricorn.
    While seeming almost emotionless on the surface, the Capricorn’s mind is always running
    on overdrive. They can often seem selfish and stingy, keeping information to themselves, or
    strategically withholding information for their own gain. Often they can be the less
    imaginative of the signs and refuse to face the facts about a situation because it would
    signal that they were wrong about something (which they hate) </string>


    <string name="capricornHiddenSide">very messy</string>

    <string name="capricornHabit">being dangerously sarcastic</string>

    <string name="capricornFear">upsetting the people they love</string>



</resources>
